# RAMADAN MUSTAPHA

# **Fullstack Developer**

+212 622 63 49 43

■ mustapha.ramadan04@gmail.com

\* Salé, Morocco.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Web Developer

### International academy

**10/2023 – 12/2023** 

Internship at an International Academy for the development of information and communication.

• Mission: Development of web applications, modification and creation of structured scripts.

# Web Developer.

#### **218LABS**

03/2023 - 09/2023

Rabat, Morocco.

Rabat, Morocco.

Internship as a Developer within a company.

- Mission: Development of web applications, modification and creation of structured scripts, processing databases, managing APIs.
- Technologies: PHP, MySQL, jQuery, Laravel, Symfony, Drupal.

#### Web Developer.

**Directorate of Public Enterprises and Privatization..** 

04/2021 – 06/2021

- Rabat, Morocco.
- Internship in the Information Systems division, Directorate of Public Companies and Privatization.
  - Mission: Creation and development of Intranet web application.
  - Technologie: Asp.net, SQL, JS, BootStrap, HTML, CSS

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Diploma Specialized Technician in IT Development**

Specialized Institute of Applied Technology.

2019 – 2021

Salé, Morocco.

#### Bachelor's degree, specialized law.

### **University Mohammed V**

2014 – 2017

Rabat, Morocco.

# High School degree in experimental science, life and earth science option.

#### **High School Al Motanabi**

2013 - 2014

Salé, Morocco.

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### Certificate Full Stack Software Engineering | Back-end.

## ALX

2023 - 2024

# **SUMMARY**

Full Stack developer passionate about creating user-friendly web applications. Mastery of both Vue, React front-end development, and Laravel .net back-end, guaranteeing a smooth user experience and efficient functionality. Willing to contribute to a collaborative team environment.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Arabic	••••
English	••••
Frensh	••••

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**



# **SOFT SKILLS**



# **CENTRES D'INTERET**

- Self-Learning
- **New Technologies**
- Sport
- Travel